

## CONTACT

paabloo.ch@gmail.com

+34 655 072 165

Barcelona, Spain

Pablo Cebollada Hernández

paablooch.github.io

PaablooCH

#### **PROJECTS**

Axolotl Engine - Starfall Rebellion

Megaman Game 2D-Plataform

Undercooked 3D-Unity-Puzzle

Deus Ex Machina In-house Engine

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

C++







Studio



**NSight** 



Git



RenderDoc



Jira



Unity

## SOFT SKILLS

Dynamic worker

Quick learner

Critical thinker

Problem solver

Adaptable and flexible person

Reliable team member, with a strong work ethic

# LANGUAGES

Spanish Native

Catalan Native

English Professional working proficiency

# PABLO CEBOLLADA

#### RENDER PROGRAMMER

#### PROFILE

I'm a junior programmer, with a strong background in the creation of applications and a passion for graphics programming. I have experience in developing 2D video games using a non-commercial engine and I've also worked on 3D game development using Unity. Recently, I focused on graphics development for my final master project. This involved creating and using shaders with OpenGL and deepening my proficiency in the C++ language.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Render & Engine Programmer (Master's project)

Horizons Games

January 2023-Present

- I've developed a series of features in the rendering system of the engine, involving the use of multiple shaders with different rendering purposes. Additionally, I worked on features for both the engine and gameplay and reviewed code.
- I possess a solid understanding of C++ and rendering techniques.

## **Software Developer**

IThink UPC

February 2022-February 2023

- Full stack developer, developing web applications for third parties.
- · Collaborating in big teams.
- Working with a multidisciplinary team.
- Utilizing the Scrum methodology with Jira to manage projects.
- · Ability to effectively communicate with customers.
- Working with the implementation of various programming patterns.

## **Software Developer (Internship)**

Telespazio Ibérica

April 2021-January 2022

- Full stack developer, developing web applications for first party.
- Met all the deadlines set by the client.
- · Utilizing the Scrum methodology.

# EDUCATION

## Master in Advanced Programming for AAA Videogames

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya - UPC BarcelonaTech - Talent School 2022 - 2023

## **Degree in Computer Science**

Universitat Politècnica de Catalunya - UPC BarcelonaTech 2017 - 2022

#### HOBBIES

I spend my spare time mostly playing video games, especially shooters and MOBAs, but recently, I've started playing JRPGs like Persona 5, and survival horrors like Signalis. Additionally, I like to read papers about rendering techniques to keep myself updated and I set aside time to practice some sports.